ANJA CHAMBERS

Enthusiastic and personable inside sales rep with 1+year of experience in the building and construction products industry. Talented at building quick rapport with prospective customers and using insights into their needs to propose attractive options and close sales. Strong track record for working efficiently under strict time pressure and meeting challenging personal targets.

654 Main Road, Cheyenne, WY 98765 a.c ha m bers@ myem a 11 .co m (678)901-2345

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INSIDE SALES REPRESENTATIVE

L&W Supply, Cheyenne, WY June2019- Present

- Present and demonstrate products and clearly explain features and benefits to clients
- Build positive links with prospective clients and maintain long-term relationships with an existing client base
- Discuss clients' needs, expectations, and budgetsand propose cost-effective solutions, capitalizing on upselling opportunities
- Process sales using the payment system, coordinate product pickups, and reorder stock to ensure a steady supply

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

Dollar Tree, Laramie, WY June 2016-June 2019

- Answered customer queries in-person and via phone and email and resolved co mp laints cou rteously and effic ien tly
- Worked closely with team mates to exceed ambitious sales goals
- Provi ded outstand in g cu stom er care and su pport, ensuring that every visitor found a suitable product for their requirements

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration

University Of Wyoming, Laramie, Wy, September2013- June 2017

Master Of Business Admi nistration University Of Wyoming, Laramie, Wy, Septem be r 2017 - Ju ne 2019

KEY SKILLS

- Custo mer service o riented
- Strong teamwork ability
- Ti me m a na gement a nd task prioritization
- Adept written and oral communicator, including via phone and email
- Excellent IT skills and thorough working knowledge of Microsoft Office Suite software
- Proven sales ability